

Katowice, Poland

**** 733 382 725

Profile

I am front-end developer with a thorough understanding of React.js and its core principles, as well as database design and front-end layout styling. I possess strong communication skills with excellent interpersonal effectiveness, in one-on-one and team interactions. In the last years, I've gained experience in designing and implementing high quality, elegant SaaS software for web and mobile applications.

Employment History

FrontEnd Developer, Selleo, Bielsko-Biala

March 2019 — Present

- creating web and mobile applications,
- cooperation with the backend team,
- cooperation with the designer,
- cooperation with the QA team,
- close cooperation with the client,

Junior FrontEnd Developer, Freelancer, Katowice

March 2018 — March 2019

- creating web applications,

Own business, Katowice

June 2009 — March 2018

 $\hbox{-} specialized BIO\hbox{-} pharmaceutical transport in controlled temperature.}$

Cargo Agent, Aer Lingus, Dublin Ireland

May 2005 — May 2009

- work in a cargo warehouse,
- loading/unloading vehicles with a forklift,
- preparing air pallets with cargo for all type of planes,
- customer service.

Education

Mechanical technician, A team of technical schools, Zawiercie September 1998 — June 2003

Courses

Bootcamp Web Developer, Kodilla

March 2018 — September 2018

Links

LinkedIn

Twitter

Skills

JavaScript
TypeScript
React
CSS3
GraphQL
Apollo
Redux
Node
Git
Cypress
React Testing Library
Figma
Code Review

Hobbies

Polish

English

Languages

Programming of course, but I also love sports:

- karate,
- motorcycles,
- American football (team Polish Championship 2014),
- running,
- crossfit.